boomfaucet.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy policy | BoomFaucet - free bitcoin faucet!

BoomFaucet.com Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.   

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address, Bitcoin Address or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you While Playing the game or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

      **•** To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 

We do not use an SSL certificate 

      **•** We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information 

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**We use cookies to:**

      **•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.   

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

However, you can still place orders . 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**     
www.boomfaucet.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**     
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.boomfaucet.com.    
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.boomfaucet.com and other sites on the Internet.     
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....    
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.boomfaucet.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  

www.boomfaucet.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.boomfaucet's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.  

**Log Files**   
Like many other Web sites, www.boomfaucet.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. 

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

** We have implemented the following: **

      **•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting 

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

Opting out:   
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf   

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously 

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. 

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: 

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page 

Users are able to change their personal information: 

      **•** By emailing us 

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking 

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We will notify the users via in site notification 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.boomfaucet.com   
  
* * *

Really, what is Bitcoin? Back in 2009, an unknown programmer (although it could be a group of programmers) under the pseudonym Satoshi Nakamoto has created a fundamentally new virtual money - Bitcoin. It was he who coined the name of the currency, and  invented alhorytm.  Although six years have passed, but until now no one knows where it came from who he was and even how to actually his name. After creating algorithm of cryptocurrency, the method of its production, he also introduced a way for storing this cryptocurrency so-called Bitcoin - a purse that is placed on your computer.

What are the main functions of cryptocurrency in general and  Bitcoin  in particular, and whether they differ from the usual fixed for all the money? Cryptocurrency fully comply and can perform all of these functions, namely to be a medium of exchange, a means of preserving and unit of account. Meanwhile, bitcoin is cryptocurrency.

Here is how Wikipedia describes the Bitcoin and cryptocurrency in general: cryptocurrency - a type of digital currency based on asymmetric encryption and the use of different cryptographic methods of protection, such as the Proof-of-work and / or Proof-of-stake. Its functioning is decentralized and takes place in a computer network.

Bitcoin has no central management and issuers. Transactions digitally signed between the two nodes are sent to all nodes of peer-to-peer network, and the data on the movement of funds stored in a distributed database. To prevent the possibility of spending other people's money, or the use of their money twice used cryptographic methods.

Short cryptocurrency it’s a money what ideally suited for the operation of the Internet, or in such networks, if they are created. Examining the topic cryptocurrency worth mentioning one more digital currency which has recently become popular. It - Laytkoin. At its core, this is the same cryptocurrency, except that the algorithm of its transactions is slightly faster from transaction Bitcoins. To draw an analogy with medieval Europe in which cash settlements bimetallism prevailed, the bitcoin and litecoin comparable to gold and silver. As a medium of exchange and crypto bitcoin and litecoin not lonely, today they already comprise dozens of different exchange quotations.

Concluding this short review, I note that cryptocurrency has the opportunity and potential to become the currency of the future. Especially if the global economic system will continue and evolve. Time will show.

* * *

In the past, people used the money as a variety of items and products. In the course were and unusual rocks and shells, and teeth of killed animals and their skin. All that is used as a means of payment is impossible to enumerate, since at different times in different regions, they differed significantly. 

Modern monetary system, which we use today, was formed in the Europe of the sixteenth - seventeenth century. The main difference between medieval and modern is that whereas in the calculation of bimetallism prevailed, giving unrestricted access to treatment, like gold and silver coins. Over time, the European countries have switched to using only gold - the so-called monometallism who introduced in England in 1816.

Life moves forward and the gold just faded into the background, giving their function to regulate cash -SDR (Special Drawing Rights). At present, there is the need to create a world currency due to the need to optimize all financial transactions. The creation of such payment instrument through which could be expressed in any other currency.

What are the characteristics of the currency necessary for it to carry out the functions delegated to it. First of all, it's high stability and liquidity, and most importantly spread it around the world. What currency of today meet these requirements? Only the US dollar, although it is not regulated and is not able to provide controlled payment transactions.

That's it for this, given the way the development of a modern economy, on the first place - crypto currency as the fittest for financial transactions. And so it becomes tender - Bitcoin. Its great advantage is that it is decentralized, independent currency. And today Bitcoins can be exchanged for any other currency in the special services in the Internet or with the help of the payment system Web Money. To do this, you only need to have a Bitcoin - a purse. It should be remembered that all operations cryptocurrency are anonymous, have no emission centers, and all transactions are carried out only in a digital format.

We can only add that one of the qualitative characteristics of Bitcoins have no control and it is not yielding to the pressure of political circumstances and the central banks of the world. Only the supply and demand form the course Bitcoins. And despite the fact that in recent years dramatically increased the number of different crypto currency, first place belongs to the Bitcoins.

* * *

Since its introduction, it was necessary to mine Bitcoins. In the beginning, it was only mining - activities for the next generation unit. To do this, use the power of your computer that is working on solving specific mathematical problems. For this miner received a reward of cryptocurrency - Bitcoin.

But over time, the complexity of the problems risen, leading to an increase in the effort to mine Bitcoins. And if at the beginning of the home computer for this fully enough, now it requires much more power. Mining is carried out on the high end gaming video cards and even a dedicated device for the production of Bitcoin.

Imagine the power of a single graphics card Radeon HD +7990 gigahash was 1,2 per second and consume hundreds of watts of power, while the system is in use today ASIC Red Fury able to issue 2,5 gigahash per second, and that the consumption of only 2,5 watts.

Over time, there were a group of diggers, so-called "pools", where users  provide in common use power  their own computers where each received a fee depending on their contribution to the common cause.

The next step was the creation of the so-called Bitcoin - farms, the largest of which is located in Hong Kong. At the time of launch it was producing 26 Bitcoins per day.

As a result of this award for the creation of each new unit is gradually reduced.

Is there  another way to mine Bitcoins cryptocurrency and including? Yes there is. It cryptocurrency  or Bitcoin Faucet - passive and without expensive way to get crypto currency. How does this happen? You go to the appropriate site and perform certain actions. This may be the introduction of "captcha" and participate in a game or lottery. For this you get a certain amount of "Satoshi" (this is the smallest particle of Bitcoins equal - 0.00000001 BTC)

In order to make a profit on the Bitcoin-Faucet, you need to have a Bitcoin wallet, or if you also collect other crypto currency, the purse for this currency. When you got your wallet, you can start making "Satoshi". To do this, go to the site hosting the Bitcoin-Faucet, enter the address of your Bitcoin wallet, enter the "captcha" and forward…

* * *

Almost a year has passed since the time when Bitcoin became a stumbling rock for the crypto-currency community. At the moment an uneasy truce continues between the fans of multiple blockchain apps, Ethereum platform, and various projects of big banks that financed the creation of their own blockchain projects.

The big Bitcoin discussion started with the publication of the article series by Gavin Andresen in spring 2015, who advocated the increase of everyday transactions to 200 thousand. However, his arguments met frantic opposition within the community. After some time a small confrontation grew into massive conflict.

In view of these people, who had stood at the origins of the crypto-currency, suffered. Because of the aggressive critics and real crackdowns on his point of view Mike Hearn changed the workplace to R3. Gregory Maxwell, in his turn, felt heavy critics from the followers of the opposite camp, he was almost named Judah. Blocksteam in their lips sounded like swear-word. 

Right now the discussion is on the level when any reasoned point of view can become too subtle. Majority keeps to the neutral position. Twitter struggles calmed down as well. One may think that peace has come, all arguments have been already sounded, and everyone is right in his way.

The size of blockchain at the moment is around 60 GB according to the resource blockchain.info, increasing for 5 GB during the last month. If such tempo preserves, it will make 50 GB per year. Such quick grow will increase the nodes expenses.

The compromise was reached with the help of Segwit, which should increase current transaction capacity to 1.6-1.7 MB with the additional hard fork – to 4 MB in 2017 year.

The time has come to bury the hatchet and unite again. The demand for more Bitcoin programmers exists. The loss of anyone will make the community worry again and again. So one should round out rough corners and grow the trust of users to crypto-currency. The multiple views are not a problem, since the truth is born of arguments. Another point of view is not the reason for ostracism.

Bitcoin Classic has at the moment nearly 6% of the general volume of Bitcoin-hash and develops the ideas of the SPV, when the Bitcoin Core experiments with the Segwit ideas. It is a new alive ecosystem, where new ideas and creative potential can make progress.
